

About Me

I was born and raised in Bangladesh, and now I'm proud to be raising my young family here. That's why I love helping people find their Bangladesh dream home. Having lived and worked here nearly my entire life,

Expertise Skill

- Freshwater Fish Culture
- Fish Breeding
- Pen & Cage Culture
- Fish Transpotation
- Fish Processing

Contact Me

- +880-1813770773
- junayedkarim111@gmail.com
- Bhubanghar, Bhubanghar, Cumilla, Cumilla-3500

Language

Native-Banguli Expert-English Basic-Hindi

Junayed Karim

Aquaculture Specialist

Education

- Secondary School
 Certificate (2012-2013)
 Passing Year-2014
 Resut (GPA)-4.88
- Higher Secondary School
 Certificate(2014-2015
 Passing Year-2016
 Resut(GPA)-5.00
- Undergraduate
 Noakhali Science and Technology University
 Fisheries and Marine Science
 Complate 7th Semister and Continue last semister.
 Result-Avarage CGPA 3.'55

Work Experience

- Nursery InstructorSotota Fish Hatchery 2020present.
- Project ManagerFish Culture Private LTD.I 2018-2020
- OwnerAquafram Fisheries LTD.(Rearing)-Current
- SuperviserTilapia Breeding Hatchery I 2017-2018